One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Thank You For Loving Me
Ace...
Ace!
Ace-san!
He's been beaten! Dammit!
Stop Akainu!
Fire!
How will this war end?
No way! Is he a monster?!
So you're still alive, then?
Stop...
Stop!
Jinbe!
You can't touch him anymore!
You're just delaying the inevitable, Jinbe!
Since you used to be a Warlord...
you should know exactly how strong I am.
If I can buy us some time by risking my life, then I'll gladly do so!
I've been prepared to die from the very beginning!
Jinbe!
Marco! That guy's here!
Gee, thank you for helping me! I almost died...
Just shut up and unlock this thing!
V-Vice Admiral Garp!
What are you...?
Garp!
What are you doing?! Have you lost your mind?!
You better keep holding me down, Sengoku!
Because if you don't, I will kill Sakazuki!
You fool!
I guess I need to execute a traitor, too.
Jinbe, get down!
How annoying!
So you guys are Haki users!
How could we let that happen?!
I'll never forgive myself for this!
Can't you see that Fire Fist can't be saved?
Take a look!
Ace...
Hey, are you all right? Hey.
Ace, you need to get treated right away!
I'm sorry, Luffy...
Huh?
To save me...
you pushed yourself so hard...
but I won't be able to make it out of here...
I'm sorry.
Wh-What are you saying?
Don't be ridiculous!
Somebody, treat him!
Please! Please help Ace!
Hey, somebody! Help Ace! Please!
Hurry! This way! Give him first aid now!
Okay!
Straw Hat-boy...
Ace! Are you all right?!
Hurry up and treat him!
Okay, let me see the wound!
Please!
This is...!
Huh?
Hey.
What's the matter? Hurry up and help him!
I'm sorry.
What do you mean by that?
What's going on?! Just do something!
Hey, aren't you a doctor?! Hey!
It's no use.
My organs have been burned.
I'm not gonna last long.
I can tell...
that my life is ending...
Ace...
what are you saying?
Are you gonna die?!
You promised me...
that you'd never die...
no matter what, Ace!
I would've given up a long time ago...
if it weren't for Sabo and a
high-maintenance brother like you.
If Gold Roger had a kid?
Of course I know what'd happen to him!
They'd get their head cut off for sure!
No way! I wouldn't be happy if the kid died that easily.
How about shoving needles into that kid until the number equals the people that hated Roger!
No way! We should burn him at the stake...
and humiliate him in front of the whole world!
That sounds nice!
They'll all say: "It serves you right!"
I'd want his last words to be...
"I'm sorry I was born. I'm nothing but trash."
Ah, well... I doubt that brat actually exists.
No one wanted me to exist.
Ace! Did you start trouble in town again?
Everybody is talking about it!
Why can't you stay out of trouble for our sake?
Shut up, Dadan!
What?!
If I was stronger, I would've killed them all.
Oh yeah. If you ever see Dadan again... can you give her my regards?
Facing my own death, I even miss a woman like her.
Like I said, don't say that you're gonna die!
There is one thing... that makes me want to stay...
That's my desire to see you fulfill your dream.
But... I know you can do it!
Because you're my little brother!
Just like how I swore on that day...
I have no regrets...
in my life.
Liar! You're lying!
I'm not lying.
I've realized that what I really wanted... wasn't fame.
Did I deserve to be born?
I wanted to know the answer to that question.
Become my son!
I take it my beloved son is still doing well?
I'm your brother!
Say whatever the hell you want!
I'm saving you, even if I die!
Men!
Rescue Ace, and destroy the Navy!
I'm not able to shout loudly enough for everyone to hear me anymore...
Could you tell them...
the words I'm about to say?
Pops...
Everybody...
And you, Luffy.
I've always been such a hopeless person...
I was demon spawn... the son of the devil...
Thank you...
for loving me!
Gramps.
Was it...
good that I was born?
Well, you...
As long as you're alive, you'll figure it out eventually.
Ace...
Did you think I was dead?
But...!
What are you crying about?! I'm alive, you idiot!
I promise you... I will never die!
How could I leave a wimpy
little brother like you behind?
Garp.
Take care of my child.
Our child's name is Gol D. Ace.
Didn't ya know? When you exchange sake cups, you become brothers.
From today onward...
we are brothers!
Editing, Sewil
Quality Control, Feeso, Galaxy 9000, Pepperjack
Timing, Galaxy 9000
Translation, Crunchyroll
Visual Effects, Datenshi, KaitouYahiko
Graphics, Datenshi
Karaoke, KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking, Halee
Raws, OPFans